{
    "posts": [{
            "id": 1,
            "title": "json-server",
            "author": "typicode"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "userid": "",
            "author": "dsad"
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": 0,
            "QuestionCategory": "general",
            "Answer": "java is a programming language",
            "CreatedBy": "Ram",
            "UpdatedBy": "Sohan",
            "id": 3
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "234",
            "Question": "Whats the time?",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "its 5 ",
            "CreatedBy": "General",
            "UpdatedBy": "Lorem ipsum",
            "id": 4
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "24",
            "Question": "What are you doing?",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "sda",
            "CreatedBy": "gen",
            "UpdatedBy": "dsada",
            "id": 5
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "34",
            "Question": "Whats going on..?",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "dfssf",
            "CreatedBy": "fdsf",
            "UpdatedBy": "fdsf",
            "id": 6
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "324",
            "Question": "Wlasd",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "klkf",
            "CreatedBy": "kldfs",
            "UpdatedBy": "ldskf",
            "id": 7
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "432",
            "Question": "dadsad",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "dsfsd",
            "CreatedBy": "dsad",
            "UpdatedBy": "dsad",
            "id": 8
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "4432",
            "Question": "sd fdfds",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "das das",
            "CreatedBy": "d asd",
            "UpdatedBy": " asd",
            "id": 9
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "434",
            "Question": "sdasd",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "sad as",
            "CreatedBy": "dasdas",
            "UpdatedBy": "dasdas",
            "id": 10
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "32423",
            "Question": "edasd",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "dasdas",
            "CreatedBy": "dsadas",
            "UpdatedBy": "dasdas",
            "id": 11
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "23424",
            "Question": "dsajdljas",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "dsfaf",
            "CreatedBy": "dsadas",
            "UpdatedBy": "dasdasd",
            "id": 12
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "4234",
            "Question": "hjhdkas",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "kjlkjf",
            "CreatedBy": "jklfjdslk",
            "UpdatedBy": "jkdsjflsk",
            "id": 13
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "1414",
            "Question": "dasdas",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "dsda",
            "CreatedBy": "dsadsa",
            "UpdatedBy": "dasda",
            "id": 14
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "79879",
            "Question": "dsfdsf",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "kldfk;ls",
            "CreatedBy": "kl;dskf;",
            "UpdatedBy": "klkdf;sl",
            "id": 15
        },
        {
            "QuestionId": "890",
            "Question": "sadkajda",
            "QuestionCategory": "",
            "Answer": "kjfdklsfj",
            "CreatedBy": "kjdsjflk",
            "UpdatedBy": "kdsjfl",
            "id": 16
        }
    ],
    "comments": [{
        "id": 1,
        "body": "some comment",
        "postId": 1
    }],
    "profile": {
        "name": "typicode"
    }
}